tecnigen.com 2014-06-22

# Privacy Policy of Tecnigen.comTecnigen – A True Tech & Social News Blog

If you need more information or have any questions or doubts about our privacy policy then please feel free to contact us here

You you want details about Copyright Policy then please [visit here](http://www.tecnigen.com/copyright-policy/)

At Tecnigen.com, the privacy of our readers or visitors is of really high importance to us. This Legal Privacy Policy Document gives declaration about types of personal or private information which is received as well as collected by techigen.com and how we use these information.

###  Log Files 

Same as other website, tecnigen.com makes legal use of log files and data.

The information which we term inside the log file exactly includes :

  * Internet Protocol (IP Address)
  * Type of Browser used
  * Information about Internet Service Provider (ISP)
  * Date as well as exact time of visit (stamp)
  * Referring as well as exit pages
  * We do use analytic tools to check the number of clicks
  * Administer the website
  * Tracks and keep the record of readers/visitors/user’s activity on website
  * We do use and keep demographic information

Note : IP address and such type of other information are not linked to any data which is personally identifiable.

Note : Your details which we got from log files, cookies, etc will never be revealed to any agency or third party people at any cost. We do respect your privacy and our privacy policy. 

###  Cookies And Web Beacons 

Tecnigen.com uses cookies to store vital information about our readers/users/visitors preferences, previous records, other specific information on which user visits the page which includes browser information and so.

###  DoubleClick DART Cookie 

  * Google.com, as a third party vendor does use cookies to serve advertisements on tecnigen.com
  * Google.com also uses DART cookie to serve ads to users based on their visit to tecnigen.com as well as other websites too
  * If user wishes or want to opt out of the use of DART cookie then he can visit the Google ad & content network privacy policy at their official web page. URL - [http://www.google.com/privacy ads.html](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

We are also partnered as a third party member to advertising partners like Google Adsense and Chitika and they may use cookies as well as web beacons on tecnigen.com

Above mentioned third-party advertisement networks also uses the same technology on tecnigen.com when user/visitor/reader clicks on advertisement served by them on our website. They may use vital information like IP address, browser, location, etc on behalf of their terms. They may use information which is taken from our technology or cookies.

Hereby, we confirm that, we don’t have access to any of the third-party cookies which is used our advertisers and so we don’t have any control over it.

If you have further questions about these third-party cookies then please contact the respective advertisers for more information. We hereby firmly confirm that we cannot control the activities of such other advertisers on our website.

If you want to disable cookies then you can use certain software of can go through the settings in your internet browser options.

If you still have any queries about privacy policy then please feel free to contact our team at

techmero[at]gmail.com

+918866990446
